Inventory of the Ginetta Sagan papers
Hoover Institution Archives
Ginetta Sagan papers
1941-2006
83017
Hoover Institution Archives
343 manuscript boxes, 4 oversize boxes, 4 card file boxes, 1 oversize folder, 2 phonorecords, digital files (148.1 linear feet)
Memoirs, correspondence, minutes, financial records, press releases, reports, interview transcripts, notes, lists, questionnaires, news dispatches, printed matter, and audiovisual material relating to civil liberties, political prisoners, and refugees, especially in Vietnam and Cambodia. Includes records of the Aurora Foundation, Amnesty International, and Humanitas.
Sagan, Ginetta
Access
Collection is open for research.
Collection stored off site; a minimum of two days notice is required for use. Boxes may be requested through Stanford's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/
Use copies of some videorecordings are available. To listen to sound recordings or to view other videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in multiple increments between 1983 and 2011.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Materials
Amnesty International of the USA, Inc.: National Office records, Columbia University
Giuliana Beltrami papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Rose Burgunder Styron interview, Hoover Institution Archives
Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records, Stanford University Archives
Zbigniew Romaszewski papers, Hoover Institution Archives
Biographical Note
American human rights advocate; West Coast coordinator, Amnesty International; vice president, Humanitas; executive director, Aurora Foundation.
Ginetta Sagan was born Teresa Moroni in San Colombano al Lambro, Italy on June 1, 1923. In September 1943, she joined the Italian anti-fascist group Giustizia e Libertà, delivering copies of underground newspapers and gathering intelligence on the location and status of partisan prisoners. After the war, during which she sustained injuries, she recuperated at the Casa di Cura Vallesana in Sondalo, Italy. In 1949, she moved to Paris, France, where she lived at the residence of Joshua G. B. Campbell, a banker and former American Field Service ambulance driver, referred to in her papers as "Papi." She studied psychology at the Sorbonne and met the professor Georges Verdeaux, a specialist in electroencephalography (EEG), who referred her to study psychology at the University of Illinois-Chicago.
In September 1951, she moved to Illinois and met Leonard Sagan, a Stanford graduate studying medicine at the University of Chicago. The two married on March 14, 1952 and had three sons. In 1961, the Sagan family moved to Nagasaki, Japan, where Leonard worked as the medical department chief of the Atomic Bomb Casualty Commission. During this time, Ginetta volunteered at an orphanage and organized events for local children. The family returned to the United States in 1964 and, after a year in Boston where Leonard studied at Harvard, the family settled in Washington, D.C. Ginetta continued her volunteer work and joined Amnesty International in 1967.
Leonard Sagan accepted a position at the Palo Alto Medical Clinic and the family moved to Atherton, California in 1968. Shortly after, Ginetta founded the first Amnesty International chapter on the west coast. Formally recognized as Group 19 by Amnesty in 1971, Sagan's group provided the basis for Amnesty's Western Regional Office. Within the following year, Sagan established Amnesty's Urgent Action direct mailing campaign, the First Appeal Pledge Program, and organized a benefit concert for Greek prisoners of conscience with Joan Baez and Melina Mercouri. Baez, who became a lifelong friend of Sagan, described their working relationship in her 1987 memoir And a Voice to Sing With.
After her successes on the west coast, Sagan was appointed to the national board of directors of Amnesty International USA. She served twice: from 1973 to 1976 and again from 1983 to 1987. In her first term, she co-organized the first conference for Amnesty's Campaign for the Abolition of Torture, assisted prisoners of conscience in Chile and Argentina, and co-founded AIUSA's newsletter Matchbox. In her second term, she chaired the 25th anniversary committee and organized concerts and other fundraisers.
In 1979, Joan Baez appointed Sagan to the board of directors of Humanitas, a human-rights organization dedicated to assisting Vietnamese refugees and other individuals outside Amnesty's mandate. Under the auspices of Humanitas, Sagan travelled to Paris to interview former prisoners of Vietnamese reeducation camps, including Doan Van Toai, author of Le Goulag vietnamien. The oral histories and documentation she collected provided the basis for her 1983 report, Violations of Human Rights in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, April 30, 1975 - April 30, 1983. Sagan published a revised edition in 1989.
In April 1981, Sagan established the Aurora Foundation to research human rights violations and assist victims in Poland and Vietnam. Sagan made two trips to Poland in 1985 and 1987 to meet Solidarity members Lech Wałęsa, Henryk Jankowski, and Zbigniew Romaszewski. Working closely with Barbara Piasecka Johnson, Sagan provided financial assistance to Solidarity members and their families. In 1987, Sagan honored Romaszewski with an Aurora Foundation award for human rights. Held at Stanford's Memorial Church, the ceremony featured Czesław Miłosz accepting the award on Romaszewski's behalf.
From 1986 to 1990, Sagan was a research scholar at Stanford's Institute for the Study of Women and Gender, where she researched the role of women in the Italian resistance and drafted a memoir of her World War II years. Although neither work was ever completed, Sagan later self-published a book of recipes and essays in 1994, Ginetta Sagan: A Culinary Biography (Box 254).
Until her death in 2000, Sagan served as executive director of the Aurora Foundation and activist for Amnesty International. Named honorary chair of Amnesty International USA in 1994, Sagan established Amnesty's Ginetta Sagan Fund, which continues to give an annual award for outstanding achievement in human rights.
For her service during World War II and her human rights activism, Sagan was awarded the following: La croce al merito di Guerra, Italy (1968); Italo-American Woman of the Year (1980); honorary doctorate, Starr King School (1981); Jefferson Award (1987); Albert Schweitzer Award from Chapman College (1990); Grande Ufficiale Ordine al Merito della Repubblica Italiana (1995); the U.S. Presidential Medal of Freedom (1996); and the Order of Merit of the Republic of Poland (2010).
Scope and Content of Collection
The papers document the life and work of human rights activist Ginetta Sagan through memoirs, oral history interviews, correspondence, press releases, reports, transcripts, notes, lists, questionnaires, news dispatches, printed matter, videos, and sound recordings. Sagan's papers also contain records of three different human rights organizations: Amnesty International, founded in 1961 by Peter Benenson; Humanitas, founded in 1979 by Joan Baez; and the Aurora Foundation, founded in 1981 by Ginetta Sagan.
Acquired in more than twenty separate increments from 1983 to 2011, the papers remain in the order received from the donor. When available, original folder titles have been retained. An index to major groups represented in Sagan's papers is included in this inventory; researchers should note, however, that not all items fall within the groups listed. The bulk of Sagan's papers consists of Aurora Foundation and Amnesty International records, as well as Vietnam research materials used to write two editions of Violations of Human Rights in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam.
Sagan researched human rights violations throughout the world, but her activism, fundraising, and writing were focused primarily on prisoners of conscience in Cambodia, Chile, Czechoslovakia, Greece, Poland, and Vietnam. These materials include correspondence, interview transcripts, research materials, and writings documenting human rights violations. Of particular interest are sound recordings and video tapes of activists Joan Baez, Lech Wałęsa, François Ponchaud, and former prisoners of Vietnamese reeducation camps.
As a scholar at Stanford University's Institute for Research on Women and Gender from 1986 to 1990, Sagan researched the role of women in the Italian resistance during World War II, materials of which can be found in the Italian resistance research group.
Received in 2011, boxes 282 to 351 and oversize materials in box 93 contain the last increment to Ginetta Sagan's papers. This portion of the collection was assembled by Sim Smiley, a researcher hired by the Aurora Foundation to document Sagan's life. Comprised mainly of biographical materials such as oral history transcripts, photographs, correspondence, and memoirs, the papers provide more comprehensive documentation of Sagan's World War II years. The last increment also contains research materials on Vietnam, the Italian resistance, and Aurora Foundation records.
Index of Major Groups
The papers are in the order in which they were received from the donor. All materials, with the exception of sound and video recordings, are in labelled folders. Most of the materials in the collection fall into the following record groups.
12-14, 19-61, 65-66, 68-72, 77, 82, 84-95, 99-138, 140-142, 149-153, 155-161, 167-181, 184, 199-224, 228-230, 232, 233, 240-246, 256, 258, 260, 264, 316, 328, 329, 337, 338, 342, 343, 345-349 Amnesty International files, 1963-2000. Contains correspondence, financial records, memoranda, board minutes, reports, clippings, collected articles, photographs, and printed matter. See also: Sound recordings and Video tapes.
45, 68, 70, 74-77, 98, 100-103, 139-148, 154-155, 159-161, 166-17, 176, 178, 180-181, 199-202, 206-209, 211-215, 217, 218, 222-228, 232, 243, 246-248, 255-258, 260, 265-279, 330-337, 339-343, 345-349, 351, Map case Aurora Foundation files, 1968-2006. Contains correspondence, notes and writings by Ginetta Sagan, drafts of speeches, financial records, memoranda, board minutes, reports, clippings, collected articles, and printed matter documenting the establishment and administration of the Foundation.
9, 33, 40, 93, 96, 97, 100, 105, 112, 117, 140, 149, 151, 153, 170, 173-175, 180-182, 199-210, 212-214, 217, 218, 222-224, 229, 232, 240, 243, 246, 254-258, 260, 279, 282-287, 291-239, 314-322, 351 Biographical files, 1940s-2000. Contains clippings, correspondence, oral history transcripts, memoirs, notes, and resumes documenting the life and activism of Ginetta Sagan. Some files were assembled by Sim Smiley, a researcher authorized by the Aurora Foundation. See also: Sound recordings and Video tapes.
10-12, 18, 54, 62, 139, 173, 180, 228, 231, 233, 251 Cambodia files, 1977-1984. Includes correspondence, clippings, collected articles, reports and an interview with François Ponchaud, author of Cambodia: Year Zero.
1-3, 53, 77, 173, 179, 202, 257 Czechoslovakia files, 1976-1987. Includes correspondence, trial transcripts, printed matter, and clippings, mainly related to the persecution of Charta 77 activists.
13, 85, 86, 119, 164, 184, 199, 202, 208, 233, 246, 316, 344 Greece files, 1967-1991. Includes correspondence, reports, printed matter, and clippings related mainly to prisoners of the Greek military junta from 1967 to 1974.
14, 15, 34, 140-142, 147, 151, 160, 180, 181, 200, 206, 210, 224, 228, 242, 303, 317 Humanitas files, 1976-1981. Includes correspondence, press releases, clippings, and memoranda documenting the founding and administration of the human rights organization founded by Joan Baez.
77, 170, 177, 180, 199-206, 213, 216, 217, 232, 240, 242, 245, 246 Italian Resistance research, 1941-2000. Includes research materials, particularly photocopies of Office of Strategic Services files from the U.S. National Archives, on Italian resistance movements during World War II.
15, 19, 26, 29, 40, 66, 69, 71, 83, 102, 107, 114, 126, 136, 140, 146, 149, 154, 161, 167, 171, 174, 179, 199-208, 211-214, 217, 218, 222, 223, 228, 232, 233, 240-242, 245, 255-257, 261, 263, 266, 276, 277, 289, 291, 292, 299, 300, 313-319, 322, 331, 335, 339, 346, 348 Photographs, 1940s-2000. Contains photographic prints, negatives, and proofsheets depicting Ginetta Sagan, her family and friends, and Aurora Foundation and Amnesty International events.
3, 63, 69, 77, 81, 101, 141, 147, 148, 150, 153, 154, 170, 171, 174, 176, 213, 214, 222, 223, 240, 246, 255, 261, 266, 319, 332, 339-340 Poland files, 1983-1996. Includes correspondence, lists of prisoners, trip summaries, financial records, clippings, and printed matter primarily related to persecution of Solidarity members and their families. Includes documentation on Barbara Piasecka Johnson, Zbigniew Romaszewski, and Lech Wałęsa. See also: Sound recordings and Video tapes.
12, 33, 81, 122, 155, 170, 180, 199, 204, 206, 211, 238, 250, 262, 263 Sound recordings, 1973-1992, undated. Includes compact sound cassettes, microcassettes, and vinyl disks comprised mainly of interviews and oral histories. Unless otherwise indicated, all sound recordings on container list are on compact sound cassette.
79-81, 203, 207, 217, 222, 223, 235, 236, 238, 239, 249, 250-254, 341 Video tapes, 1980-1999. Includes VHS, Betacam, and U-Matic tapes. Unless otherwise indicated, all video tapes on container list are on VHS.
1, 4-11, 17, 62, 64, 66, 67, 72-73, 78, 82, 83, 112, 115, 117, 158-164, 168, 171, 173, 175, 177-184, 202-205, 208-212, 224, 225-229, 242, 242, 254, 267-301-312, Map case Vietnam research materials, 1968-1992. Contains transcripts, correspondence, notebooks, clippings, collected articles, printed matter, reports, and memorabilia mainly used to write two editions of Violations of Human Rights in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam. See also: Aurora Foundation and Amnesty International.
Amnesty International.; Aurora Foundation.; Humanitas.; Audiotapes.; Civil rights--Cambodia.; Civil rights--Vietnam.; Civil rights.; Phonorecords.; Political prisoners--Vietnam.; Refugees.; Video tapes.
- Vietnam research materials, 1977-1982
  - Correspondence, transcripts, and maps of reeducation camps, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 1: 1-3)
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes transcripts of interviews conducted by Ginetta Sagan (GS) in the U.S. and France
  - Defectors file, 1977-1980
    Contains interview transcripts, lists of camps and prisoners, correspondence, and clippings
    - Hoang Huo Quynh, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 4)
    - Hoang Van Hoan, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 1: 5)
    - Le Dinh, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 6)
    - Nguyen Cong Hoan, 1977 (Box-folder 1: 7)
    - Nguyen Dinh Toan, 1977 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - Nguyen Than Vinh, 1978 (Box-folder 1: 9)
    - Tom That Long, 1979 (Box-folder 1: 10)
    - Tran Van Son, 1977 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - Truong Nhu Tang, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 12)
    - Others, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 13)
    - Accounts by defectors, 1980 (Box-folder 1: 14)
  - Lien-Lac, volume V, No. 7, 1982 March (Box-folder 1: 15)
- Czechoslovakia file, 1976-1982
  - General, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 1: 16)
  - Karel Kyncl, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 1: 17)
  - Miloslav Černý, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 1: 18)
  - Jiří Lederer, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 1: 19)
  - Rudolf Battěk, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1: 20)
  - List of Czech authorities, 1980 (Box-folder 2: 1)
  - "The Prague Trial,", 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2: 2)
    English transcripts from trial against dissidents Petr Uhl, Václav Benda, Jiří Dienstbier, Otka Bednářová, Václav Havel, and Dana Nemcová
  - Clippings and correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Rudolf Battěk, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2: 4-5)
- Thailand file, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 2: 6-7)
  Includes refugee camp profiles and clippings
- Czechoslovakia file, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 3: 1-5)
  Includes correspondence, clippings, and research materials on Charta 77 and Rudolf Battěk
- U.S.S.R. and Eastern Europe, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 3: 6)
  Includes list of prisoners in Poland and research materials on Romania, Poland, Yugoslavia, and Russia
- Vietnam research materials, 1974-1983
  - Collected articles, 1983 (Box-folder 4: 1-2)
  - Indochina Issues, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - "Selected Case Histories of Prisoners of Conscience and Other Prisoners Illustrating Amnesty International's Concerns in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam,", 1983 March 15 (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Far Eastern Economic Review, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Research materials, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Collected articles, 1983 (Box-folder 5: 1-2)
  - Stockholm Conference program, 1974 March 3 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - Congressional Research Service reports, 1977 (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - John Bunzel speech, 1981 October 20 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - S.I. Hayakawa statement, 1981 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - James Bond Stockdale writing, 1980 July 10 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Washington Post clipping, 1979 March 22 (Box-folder 5: 8)
  - Defectors file, 1977-1980
    Transcripts of interviews and clippings
    - Hoang Huo Quynh, 1980 (Box-folder 5: 9)
    - Hoang Van Hoan, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 10)
    - Nguyen Cong Hoan, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 5: 11)
    - Truong Nhu Tang, 1980 (Box-folder 5: 12)
  - Church World Service correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 5: 13)
  - Vietnamese refugee camps in Singapore, 1979 (Box-folder 5: 14)
  - Vietnamese refugee interviews conducted by GS in Paris, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - "Human Rights Violations in Vietnam," by GS, circa 1979 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - The Economist and Encounter clippings, 1979 (Box-folder 6: 3-4)
  - Doan Van Toai correspondence and clippings, 1978 (Box-folder 6: 5-6)
  - United Nations Conference on Indochinese Refugees, 1979 July (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Grenoble meeting on Vietnam, 1980 February-March (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - International Fellowship of Reconciliation press releases, 1978 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Open letters by California-based human rights groups, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Vietnamese boat people clippings, 1979 (Box-folder 7: 3-4)
  - Pete McCloskey correspondence, 1979 December (Box-folder 7: 5)
  - Far Eastern Economic Review, 1979 (Box-folder 7: 6)
- Cambodia research materials, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 7: 7)
- U.S. Senate and House directory, 1981 (Box-folder 7: 8)
- Human rights, 1978-1981
  - Department of State documents, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - "International Human Rights Law: What It Is and How it Can Be Used in Federal Courts," San Francisco Bar Association, 1982 January (Box-folder 8: 2)
  - Congressional Research Service reports, 1978 (Box-folder 8: 3)
  - Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 8: 4-5)
  - Research materials and correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 8: 6-7)
- Vietnamese refugees research materials, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 8: 8-9)
- Swedish Save the Children Fund correspondence and printed matter, 1980 (Box-folder 8: 10)
- Human rights research materials, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 8: 11-12)
- Peace Action News, 1980 (Box-folder 8: 13)
- Vietnam research materials, 1977-1981
  - American Friends Service Committee correspondence and printed matter, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 9: 1)
  - Country reports, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 9: 2)
  - Education, 1979 (Box-folder 9: 3)
  - Foreign policy, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9: 4)
  - Human rights research materials, 1971-1980 (Box-folder 9: 5)
  - Internal affairs, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 9: 6)
  - Torture, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Violations of Human Rights in the Socialist Republic of Vietnam, April 30, 1975-April 30, 1983, by GS (Box-folder 9: 8)
    Includes correspondence
- Terrorism research materials, 1978, undated (Box-folder 9: 9)
  Includes notes by GS
- David Weissbrodt report on human rights legislation, 1977 (Box-folder 9: 10)
  Includes clippings
- Jimmy Carter letter to GS, 1975 July 26 (Box-folder 9: 11)
- Biographical clipping on GS, Air California Magazine, 1978 September (Box-folder 9: 12)
- Vietnam, 1977-1982
  - Vietnamese prison camps, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 10: 1)
  - La Goulag vietnamien, by Doan Van Toai, 1978 October (Box-folder 10: 2)
  - Years of Reeducation in North Vietnam, by Tran Huynh Chau, translated by Ralph S. Carlson, undated (Box-folder 10: 3)
  - Religious policy, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10: 4-6)
  - Reeducation camps, 1979, undated (Box-folder 10: 7-9)
    Includes lists of camps and prisons
- Africa research materials, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 10: 10)
- Cambodia refugees, after 1979 (Box-folder 10: 11)
- Cambodia Action Update, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11: 1)
- Afghanistan, 1979 (Box-folder 11: 2)
- Ethiopia, 1978 (Box-folder 11: 3)
- Vietnam, 1976-1980
  - Research materials, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 11: 4-5)
  - The Smaller Dragon Under Torture, by Tran Phu Loc, 1980 (Box-folder 11: 6)
  - "American Human Rights Policy and a Southeast Asian Case Study: Vietnam," by Laola H. Hironaka, 1980 (Box-folder 11: 7)
  - Far Eastern Economic Review, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11: 8)
- Amnesty International, 1971-1982
  - Cambodia research materials, 1977-1980, undated (Box-folder 12: 1-12)
    Includes two compact sound cassettes of interviews with François Ponchaud
  - Iran, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 12: 13)
  - South Korea, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 12: 14)
  - Chile, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - China, 1980 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Cuba, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Greece, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Haiti, 1980 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Indonesia, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Latin America, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 13: 7-8)
- Humanitas, 1976-1981
  - Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 14: 1)
    Mainly letters to Humanitas president Joan Baez
  - Events file, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Cambodia Emergency Relief Fund clippings and correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - "Open letter to the Socialist Republic of Vietnam," by Joan Baez, Los Angeles Times, 1979 May 30 (Box-folder 14: 4-5)
    Includes clippings, press releases, responses and related correspondence by Baez
  - Founding documents, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Madrid Consultations on Human Rights and Disarmament, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 14: 7)
    Includes a statement by Baez
  - 7th fleet campaign and Southeast Asia trip, 1979 (Box-folder 14: 8)
    Includes Baez letter to Jimmy Carter
- Amnesty International, 1975-1982
  - Legal Committee for Human Rights, 1975 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - West Coast meeting notes, 1973 July 5 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Internal documents, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Urgent Action, 1982 (Box-folder 14: 12)
- Human Rights Internet Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 15: 1)
- Helsinki Accords, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 15: 2)
- International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box-folder 15: 3)
- Human rights international procedure, 1980 (Box-folder 15: 4)
- Humanitas, 1976-1981
  - Memo to Joan Baez, 1980 March (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Joan Baez correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Joan Baez European tour clippings, 1979 October (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Paris trip, 1980 (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Humanitas International, 1981 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Press releases, 1979 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - Conference invitations and correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 15: 11)
    Includes photographs from an event featuring GS
  - Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 15: 12-14)